(Howard:)she made some great points.
(Howard:)You and I have known each other
a long time,
(Howard:)and I didn't hear the rest
'cause she took her bra off.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)How do you propose
we move forward?
(Howard:)For starters, we could stop
insulting each other.
(Sheldon:)That's a great idea.
(Sheldon:)And in the spirit
of our new arrangement,
(Sheldon:)I will mask my surprise
that you came up with it.
(Howard:)Anyway, I got invited
to do a little talk at NASA
(Howard:)in Houston this weekend.
(Howard:)They gave me two tickets.
Bernadette can't go.
(Howard:)You want to come with me?
You can visit your mom,
(Howard:)and I'll show you
around the space center.
(Sheldon:)I have one question.
(Sheldon:)Is this a prank
where we land in Houston
(Sheldon:)and you've made up
wanted posters
(Sheldon:)that have my face with
a mustache and a Spanish name
(Sheldon:)and then I get arrested
and deported to South America?